okt.to 2017-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Oktopost

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Oktopost (the "Company", "we", "us" or "our") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") in connection with the access to or use of the Service. This Privacy Policy applies to the Service and all products and services offered by the Company. Accessing or using our Service signifies the acceptance to abide by the terms stipulated in this Privacy Policy. 

## Personal Information

The Personal Information we collect (i.e. information that may allow the identification of the User) includes information voluntarily submitted by the User, including the Users' name and email address, phone number, billing address and certain payment information (e.g. credit card's expiration date and last four digits, etc.). 

## Non-Personal Information

Non-Personal Information may include the browser name, the type of the User's device and technical information transmitted by the User's device, language preferences, time stamps and visited pages, the operating system, utilized internet service provider and other similar information. We may also collect the User's IP address which would irrevocably anonymized. 

## How We May Collect Your Information?

  * When the User voluntarily submits Personal Information (by filling out a form, subscribing to our newsletter, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available in connection with our Service); Users may always refuse to provide Personal Information. 
  * Non-Personal Information may be automatically transmitted by the User's device. 
  * When using our Service we assign the User's device with a log file, a cookie (session or persistent), web beacons or other related technologies, to collect Non-Personal Information with respect to the User's activity on our Service. 
  * A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a website assign to your device while you are viewing a web site. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and our services quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help customize your experience. You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org. You may remove our cookie by following the instructions of your device preferences; however, if you choose to disable our cookie, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited. 

## How We Use Information We Collect

We collect Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve and enhance our Service; 
  * To respond to Users' requests and feedbacks; 
  * We may send to the User's email address promotional offers, products which may interest the User, notifications, updates or surveys. The User may, at any time, request to opt-out of receiving future emails or notifications from us, by contacting us; 
  * To perform research, analytics or for statistical purposes; 
  * To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; 
  * To respond to claims that any content available through the Service violates rights of third-parties; 
  * To resolve disputes and enforce our policies, including investigation of potential violations thereof, for the purpose of law enforcement or in accordance with any applicable law or regulation. 

## With Whom We Share Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' Personal Information to other parties. We may share Personal Information with our trusted service providers only to the extent required to fulfill the purposes outlined above. 

We may transmit or store Personal Information, in different locations around the world, in particular outside the EEA. In such circumstances, we will strive to ensure that adequate measures are put in place in order to protect the User's confidentiality and rights with respect to Personal Information. 

Non-Personal Information may be shared with other third parties (including retailers, ad networks, advertising companies, service providers, media and other interested parties) in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of developing or delivering advertising (whether via our Service, or websites, applications or services of third parties), or for the purpose of improving our Service, conducting business analysis or other business purposes. This information may be combined with information we collect from other sources, to the extent that the information remains Anonymous Information. 

## Transfer of Personal Information from the EU

Since we operate globally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Information to countries outside of the European Union (EU). 

In such cases, your Personal Information will be transferred to and stored in countries which have been recognized by the European Commission ("EC") as providing adequate level of privacy and data protection. Alternatively, if your Personal Information is stored by our trusted service providers or any other third party in countries which have not been formally recognized by the EC as providing an adequate level of privacy and data protection, then we shall implement in our agreements with our trusted service providers or any other third party, special data processing contractual clauses, which have been approved by the EC as providing adequate contractual protection. 

You hereby consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to countries outside of the European Union. 

## Information Retention Policy And User choice

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion. Users may, at any time, rectify, update or withdraw Personal Information pertaining to them, by contacting us. 

Unless we are instructed otherwise by Users, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to provide the Service and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

## Children Information

We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will remove its information from our servers. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that children are not using the Service. 

## Security

We use industry standard security tools and measures, as well as internal guidelines and organizational procedures to prevent information misuse and data leakage. The information is also protected using Amazon's Web Services cloud-based computing and data storage infrastructure (Amazon S3). You may read more about how Amazon Web Services incorporates best practices concerning data security at this link: http://aws.amazon.com/security. 

While we strive to use commercially acceptable means and procedures to protect the information, which considerably reduce the risks of data misuse, we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe. If you become aware of any security vulnerability or potential data breach, please contact us immediately, and we will take the appropriate measures to address such incident, as deemed necessary. 

## Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or other corporate transaction, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign information, including Personal Information, in connection with the foregoing events. In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Service that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Service. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Service, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

## Amendment to the Privacy Policy

The Company has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage periodic review of our Privacy Policy for any changes in order to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. The last amendments will be reflected in the "Last Updated" heading. The continued use of the Service following the posting of any amendments will be deemed as acceptance of those amendments. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of our Service, please [contact us](mailto:privacy@oktopost.com).
